

PROFILE

My name is Nguyen Van Tan, majoring in Mechatronics at Ho Chi Minh city University of Technology. My strengths are fast learning, good teamwork and time management skills, always learning to develop further. My short-term goal is to improve myself in terms of work and language experience. The long-term goal is to become a manager and specialized engineer.

CONTACT

PHONE

034 339 7036 (Zalo)

MAIL

tan.nguyen20299@ gmail.com

ADRRESS

Bien Hoa City, Dong Nai Province.

SKILLS

Software:

- C Programing, Python, openCV.
- PLC, HMI.
- Mircrosoft Visual Studio.
- AutoCAD, SolidWorks.

Language:

English - Elementary

NGUYEN VAN TAN

MECHATRONIC ENGINEER

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh city University of Technology

9/2017 - 12/2021

- Major: Mechatronics Engineering
- GPA: 7.54

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUKI (Viet Nam) Co., LTD - R&D Engineer

4/2022 - Present

- Programming automatic machines (Automatic Sewing machines)
 - + Automatic control mechanisms.
 - + PLC and HMI programming.
 - + Panel programming (button, image, send/received signal) with Mainboard.
 - + Test software, debug and fix bugs.
 - + Apply image processing to the machine automatically.
- Collaborate with mechanical, electrical, and other departments to ensure project progress.

Bach Khoa Research Center for Manufacturing Engineering – R&D Intern

6/2019 - 6/2021

- Preliminary drawing of a 3D model on Solidworks.
- Design and calculate mechanical parts, edit it on the 3D drawing and export it to the 2D drawing, and edit details about the dimensions, sections... on AutoCAD.
- Design, calculate, and select equipment for the electrical of the machine. Draw electrical drawings showing control circuits, and interactions between electrical devices.
- Design control algorithms and programming PLC. Then simulate on the software to check the operation of the devices.